[
    {
        "question": "Who said 'Laugh it up fuzzball'?",
        "optionA": "Darth Vader",
        "optionB": "Princess Leia",
        "optionC": "Han Solo",
        "optionD": "R2-D2",
        "answer": "Han Solo"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who fired the shot that destroyed the Death Star?",
        "optionA": "Luke",
        "optionB": "Red #5",
        "optionC": "Han Solo",
        "optionD": "Chewbacca",
        "answer": "Luke"
    },
    {
        "question": "What year was Star Wars (episode IV: A New Hope) released?",
        "optionA": "1981",
        "optionB": "1947",
        "optionC": "1977",
        "optionD": "1979",
        "answer": "1977"
    },
    {
        "question": "What's the icy planet's name in Empire Strikes Back?",
        "optionA": "Endor",
        "optionB": "Hoth",
        "optionC": "Tattooine",
        "optionD": "Toth",
        "answer": "Hoth"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many languages does C3PO speak?",
        "optionA": "3",
        "optionB": "Over 20 thousand",
        "optionC": "Over 6 million",
        "optionD": "Over 100",
        "answer": "Over 6 million"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which large, slug-like creature is the most powerful crime boss on Tatooine?",
        "optionA": "Boba Fett",
        "optionB": "Chewbacca",
        "optionC": "Jabba-the-hut",
        "optionD": "Sebulba",
        "answer": "Jabba-the-hut"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which number order brought about the destruction of the Jedi Kinights?",
        "optionA": "66",
        "optionB": "99",
        "optionC": "77",
        "optionD": "1",
        "answer": "66"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who did Qui-Gon and Obi-Wan duel with?",
        "optionA": "Emperor Palpatine",
        "optionB": "Darth Maul",
        "optionC": "Count Dooku",
        "optionD": "Sebulba",
        "answer": "Darth Maul"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the first orders Supreme Leader?",
        "optionA": "Emperor Palpatine",
        "optionB": "Snoke",
        "optionC": "Kylo-Ren",
        "optionD": "Smaug",
        "answer": "Snoke"
    },
    {
        "question": "What's the name of Han Solo's ship?",
        "optionA": "Slave I",
        "optionB": "Millenium Eagle",
        "optionC": "Executor",
        "optionD": "Millenium Falcon",
        "answer": "Millenium Falcon"
    },

    {
        "question": "What planet are Wookies from?",
        "optionA": "Yavin",
        "optionB": "Kashyyyk",
        "optionC": "Tattoine",
        "optionD": "Endor",
        "answer": "Kashyyyk"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is Luke and Leia's mother?",
        "optionA": "Padme Amidala",
        "optionB": "Queen Latifa",
        "optionC": "Ashoka",
        "optionD": "Mon Mothma",
        "answer": "Padme Amidala"
    },
    {
        "question": "What kind of species is Sebulba?",
        "optionA": "Wookie",
        "optionB": "Gun-gun",
        "optionC": "Hut",
        "optionD": "Dug",
        "answer": "Dug"
    },
    {
        "question": "What invisible power binds the galaxy together?",
        "optionA": "The Force",
        "optionB": "Light saber",
        "optionC": "Atoms",
        "optionD": "The Tokens",
        "answer": "The Force"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where does Yoda go to live after the Jedi purge?",
        "optionA": "Yavin",
        "optionB": "Endor",
        "optionC": "Tatooine",
        "optionD": "Dagobah",
        "answer": "Dagobah"
    },
    {
        "question": "What color is Mace Windu's lightsaber?",
        "optionA": "Purple",
        "optionB": "Red",
        "optionC": "Green",
        "optionD": "Blue",
        "answer": "Purple"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which planet is covered in water, and where the clones were made?",
        "optionA": "Coruscant",
        "optionB": "Tatooine",
        "optionC": "Kamino",
        "optionD": "Kashyyyk",
        "answer": "Kamino"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is Jango Fett's son?",
        "optionA": "Boba",
        "optionB": "Snoke",
        "optionC": "Kylo-Ren",
        "optionD": "Anakin",
        "answer": "Boba"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is also known as Emperor Palpatine?",
        "optionA": "Darth Sidious",
        "optionB": "Snoke",
        "optionC": "Darth Vader",
        "optionD": "Count Dooku",
        "answer": "Darth Sidious"
    },
    {
        "question": "How did Obi-Wan kill Grievous?",
        "optionA": "Light saber",
        "optionB": "Knife",
        "optionC": "Laser Blaster",
        "optionD": "Fire",
        "answer": "Laser Blaster"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said 'it's a trap'?",
        "optionA": "Ackbar",
        "optionB": "Lando",
        "optionC": "Obi Wan",
        "optionD": "Anakin",
        "answer": "Ackbar"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many Sith are always there?",
        "optionA": "One",
        "optionB": "Two",
        "optionC": "Three",
        "optionD": "Four",
        "answer": "Two"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who killed Jabba the Hutt?",
        "optionA": "Leia",
        "optionB": "Luke",
        "optionC": "Han",
        "optionD": "Jar-Jar",
        "answer": "Leia"
    },
    {
        "question": "What did Luke lose during his fight with Vader?",
        "optionA": "His heart",
        "optionB": "Leg",
        "optionC": "Hand",
        "optionD": "Hair",
        "answer": "Hand"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where did the Clone Wars begin?",
        "optionA": "Tatooine",
        "optionB": "Geonosis",
        "optionC": "Naboo",
        "optionD": "Jakku",
        "answer": "Geonosis"
    }

]